export default [
{
            id: 1,
            question: 'What is 7 - 4 ?',
            answers: ['3','0','2','1'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 2,
            question: 'What is 7 - 5 ?',
            answers: ['-1','2','1','0'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 3,
            question: 'What is 7 - 6 ?',
            answers: ['0','-1','1','-2'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 4,
            question: 'What is 7 - 7 ?',
            answers: ['-2','0','-1','-3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 5,
            question: 'What is 8 - 4 ?',
            answers: ['1','2','3','4'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 6,
            question: 'What is 8 - 5 ?',
            answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 7,
            question: 'What is 8 - 6 ?',
            answers: ['1','-1','2','0'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 8,
            question: 'What is 8 - 7 ?',
            answers: ['1','-2','-1','0'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 9,
            question: 'What is 9 - 4 ?',
            answers: ['5','3','2','4'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 10,
            question: 'What is 9 - 5 ?',
            answers: ['2','1','4','3'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 11,
            question: 'What is 9 - 6 ?',
            answers: ['2','3','0','1'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 12,
            question: 'What is 9 - 7 ?',
            answers: ['1','-1','0','2'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
]
